We'll be right back.
Get it in your sights, men!
It's a trench mortar.
Gamora, dodge!
Damn, bastards had an ambush waiting for us.
Taking the main road sure was a bad idea.
Turn around, quick!
Not so fast!
Sorry, Sodom.
Stop right there!
Chopper.
Who could be calling?
Yes?
Hello?
Howdy, howdy!
Granny Tokoro!
What's going on?
All right, sounds like you're still alive.
So where are you?
We're almost at the courthouse, but we're under attack.
Why do you ask?
Oh, perfect timing.
There's a little something I forgot to tell you.
That doesn't sound reassuring.
Well, I'm sure you're busy, so I'll make it quick.
Listen carefully.
If you remember that map Pauly drew, you might notice there's no path from the courthouse to the gates of justice.
That's been bothering me, but I was afraid to ask about it.
Look at the courthouse.
You see those towers on either side?
Yeah, I see them.
All right.
Now there's a lever on the top floor of each of those towers.
If you folks can get in there and pull both of them, a drawbridge will come down from the courthouse to the gates of justice.
Whoa!
But how do you know about all that stuff, Granny?
I came here with Tom ages ago to fix that bridge.
Damn stupid ungrateful government!
Don't take it out on me.
Chimney wants to talk, too.
Pirate Lady!
Hey, can you hear me?
Hello!
Yeah, I've got you loud and clear.
Guess what?
I just saw your rubber pirate buddy.
He was over on the rooftop of the courthouse just now.
Yeah!
So that's where he is.
There was a bunch of smoke and broken stuff up there, too, so it looks like he's wrecking the place.
Thanks.
Hopefully we'll get there soon.
And by the way, don't hang up the transponder snail.
I'd like to keep track of what's going on with you folks.
No problem.
See ya.
Can't keep the captain waiting.
Right, men?
Get out!
Good.
You head straight for the courthouse.
The sooner that your crew can get back together, the better.
That's what I say.
Sounds good.
Meanwhile, we'll split into two groups and bring down the drawbridge.
You hear that, Gamora?
To the courthouse!
Gamora!
Damn.
Who the hell is that?
Don't get too cocky, scumbags.
All right, the second one's down too.
How's that, huh?
Not so fast now, are you?
Everybody move in!
Attention all Marine Guards!
Here in Block D in the Southeast Quadrant,
the Pirate's King Bull has been eliminated.
All units should move in immediately.
Form a Block 8 around the entire area.
I repeat, all military personnel surround Block D now.
Seems that the jurymen have delivered the verdict for us.
And it's guilty as usual, huh?
Say something, man!
Sir!
Yes, sir! On our way!
The Marines we trampled over are catching up to us again.
Not good.
And it's not just them!
We're surrounded here!
We've got trench porters aimed at us, too!
There's got to be like a million bajillion of those guys out there!
We can't even run away anymore!
What are we going to do?
No!
What is this?
An earthquake?
No!
Oh my God!
Hmm!
No!
Oh…
Oh, my God!
Oh, I'm gonna talk gold!
Oh...
Oh, my God!
Oh!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Crush those criminals into the ground!
Grind their little bones between your toes, Giants!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Found him, Kashi!
Pulverizer, Limo!
Come on! What are you big locks waiting for?
Make them pay!
Ugh!
You bastards!
How dare you!
Lies!
What the hell?
Don't tell me they betrayed us!
And now, with our bosses safe,
before we mourn all those years we wasted,
we're gonna let out every last ounce of our anger on you!
Are you ready?
King of the snipers?
Let us not waste words!
Voice the signal for the counter-attack!
Soon we shall be reunited with our comrades!
Who sheuk!
M
Dammed, you got it good!
Not everyone gets their own rescue squad!
Damn, you got it good.
Not everyone gets their own rescue squad.
Hey, keep it down!
Sorry!
Huh.
Well, just saying.
It's not like I'm bitter because my men aren't coming to save me.
They got better stuff to do, I'm sure.
Ah!
Oh!
Ah, that's right.
I almost forgot.
Before you leave, you should take these with you.
Ah!
Wait a sec!
Those are devil fruits, aren't they?
Yo-yo!
Oy!
My!
What a surprise!
Cha-ba-ba!
I've never seen one in person before!
It's my first time as well!
Ah!
Stay away!
Don't let those things near me!
You ate one too.
What's your problem?
Why the fuss?
What?
Haven't you heard?
The reason they're called devil fruits is because the people who eat them have a little devil
living inside their bodies.
Just think.
If I get too close to one of those things, the devil inside me might pop out and start fighting
with the devil inside the fruit!
If that happens, my whole body will be blown to bits!
You're kidding me.
Huh.
Hmm.
That's nonsense.
You're a member of an intelligence agency, and you believe that?
What a shame.
The condition for the transfer of devil fruit powers has been confirmed by scientists on
the Grand Line for quite some time.
The condition you're talking about only happens when someone eats two devil fruits.
I don't know if devils are involved, but their bodies do burst apart.
The price for greed.
What fools.
If you think about the risk that comes with eating one fruit, you can only imagine what
kind of disaster you might bring upon yourself by eating two of them.
Huh.
So that's how it works.
Still, I'm surprised.
I can't believe you got two of these.
Pretty impressive, Chief.
How'd you pull that one?
Let's just say I have connections, how's that?
At any rate, best of luck.
That's right, CP-9.
Grow stronger and stronger.
As always, there is a certain risk involved.
We don't know what kind of devils reside in those fruits.
I've never seen a fruit like this in any reference book.
You can feel a strange power coming from them.
A heaviness in the air.
It's like they're from a different world.
That's what everyone says.
I've been told that you only learn the name of the fruit once you absorb its powers.
But there's no guessing what kind of ability you'll gain.
Well, there's no denying that there's a risk involved.
The wrong power could ruin your life.
And either way, you'll no longer be able to swim.
It's not an issue of what power you get, but how you use it.
No matter what, you won't get weaker.
And as for being unable to swim, it's hardly a problem.
It's a rare treasure of the thousands who search for them.
I'm sure most end up empty-handed or dead by the end of their journey.
Just try it already.
It'll be interesting.
Don't do it!
Are you crazy?
That thing's evil!
Also, they taste like crap, I tell you!
Crap!
Yeah, right.
He's jealous!
He doesn't want them getting stronger, Chabba-Bah!
Shame!
You should know, Chabbera,
that envy and resentment are a man's downfall!
Yo-yo-y!
Hey! Shut up!
Come on, just stop!
Think about this!
If you sell these things, you could make millions!
But one bite and you'll be cursed for the rest of your life!
Huh?
Ah!
Chabba-Bah!
Yep. Interesting, all right.
Here goes. Hope it's good.
Ah! They ate them!
No!
Brac-coo! Brac-coo-coo!
Chabba-Bah!
What's wrong?
Yo-yo-yo!
Is your body besieged with a strange metamorphosis?
Chabba-Bah!
Gros.
Guys, no sooner!
It's really gross.
Yeah, we got that, Chabba-Bah!
and yet you ate the whole thing without a word well come on try doing something already
i want to see what kind of powers you got i don't feel as if anything is different soon
you'll understand the extent of your changes the birth of new devil fruit users is always exciting
enjoy yourselves but i'd try to get those powers under control while you still can
depending on our orders you might have to use them in real combat soon
it seems bluno couldn't wait we'll have to see if he saves any fun for us
you
I'll see you next time.
In the history of this island, this is without a doubt the absolute worst thing that has ever happened in any slobby.
What the hell's going on?
On the next One Piece, almost to Loopy, gather at the Courthouse Plaza.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.